(Leonard:)Did something happen today
that's bothering you?
(Sheldon:)Well, I did mention
(Sheldon:)the Mars Rover incident
to that FBI agent
(Sheldon:)and probably cost Howard
his security clearance.
(Leonard:)What?
But why should that keep me up?
(Leonard:)Because you feel guilty?
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)So you're saying my insomnia is
caused by a guilty conscience.
(Sheldon:)Actually,
you don't have insomnia.
(Leonard:)You're sleeping now.
(Page:)Excuse me?
(Leonard:)You're having
a guilt-ridden dream.
(Sheldon:)Do you have any evidence
to support that hypothesis?
(Leonard:)How about that Gorn
sitting on the couch?
(Sheldon:)That seems fairly conclusive.
(Sheldon:)No, Gorn, no.
(Sheldon:)That's where I sit.
(Sheldon:)Thank you for agreeing
to see me, Agent Page.
Thank you for filing a complaint
with my superior, Dr. Cooper.
(Page:)I understand
you want to recant
(Page:)your statement
about Howard Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)Yes.
Was your statement untrue?